The Aftermath is a war, drama, romance film directed by James Kent.
In the aftermath of World War II, a British colonel and his wife are assigned to live in Hamburg during the
post-war reconstruction, but tensions arise with the German widower who lives with them.
Rachael Morgan, played by Keira Knightley.
Stefan Lubert, played by Alexander Skarsgård.
Lewis Morgan, played by Jason Clarke.
Burnham, played by Martin Compston.
Susan Burnham, played by Kate Phillips.
Freda Lubert, played by Flora Thiemann.
The Aftermath is a 2019 drama film directed by James Kent and written by Joe Shrapnel and
Anna Waterhouse, based on the 2014 novel of the same name by Rhidian Brook.
It stars Keira Knightley, Alexander Skarsgård and Jason Clarke.
The film had its world premiere at the Glasgow
Film Festival on 26 February 2019.
It was released in the United States on 15 March
2019, by Fox Searchlight Pictures.
It is the last Fox Searchlight Pictures film to be released
before the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, world war ii,
post war germany, post world war ii, hamburg, germany.
The tone is emotional.